# Saleh Salehizadeh

Web Developer

\$\psi\$ +90 (552) 750 8957
 □ animatorsaleh@gmail.com
 □ saleh-salehizadeh
 ⊕ SirSaleh
 ⊇ sirsaleh

## Summary

I am Saleh. A full-stack web developer and statistics enthusiast. since childhood, I've been programming for fun, and now I'm developing web for almost 7 years. my main fields of working were entertainment and transportation industries, using Django, PHP, R, MySQL, PostgreSQL and etc. Creating Interesting and useful systems is what connects all my interests and experiences.

#### Education

2015-2018 M.Sc., Amirkabir University of Technology, Tehran, Mathematical Statistics.

MSc. Thesis

title Simultaneous Tests For High Dimensional Datasets

description Nowadays emergence of new technologies like DNA Mircro-array has been leaded to creating large scale data, which needs new method to analysis. In my Thesis I investigated a model that works on this settings.

2010–2014 B.Sc., Allameh Tababaei University, Tehran, Applied Statistics.

BSc. Project

title Investigation on Mobile-Bank Service Based on SERVQUAL Model

#### Experience

April 2022 - Programmer, LightBlender, Bitparsers Inc. Remote Canada.

Present LightBlender is a video mapping system for LED strips. Using my experience in python and my knowledge of image processing and my previous projects (LightShifter and Lumos), I developed a new system from scratch that eliminates our need for third-party mapping system like MadMapper or Resolume, So in a stand-alone way it can handle LED strip effects.

Technologies: Flask, Python, JavaScript, Raspberry Pie, jQuery, WS1228B Led Boards and etc.

October 2021 Full-Stack developer, Trade-forward Project, Shinbob Co. Remote Canada.

- December Trade-forward is a B2B shop, which users can buy their stuff, and purchase other users' useful stuff. I am implementing the schema, restful API and etc.

Technologies: Django, DRF, nginx, postgresql, jQuery and etc.

Auguest 2021 Full-Stack developer, Lumos v1 Project, Shinbob sole. Remote Canada.

now Lumos is a PWA (progressive web application) which easily using to control the mapping systems (like madMapper or Resolume). I implemented the Database schema, api, react components and etc.

Technologies: **Software and languages** raspberry pie, Django, DRF, react-js, nginx, node-osc, postgresql and etc. **Hardware**: *Raspberry-pie*, *Minix*, and etc.

April 2021- Full-Stack developer, Lightshifter v2 Project, Shinbob sole. Remote Canada.

July 2021 Lightshifter v2 is a video mapping web-based system, which can connect to mapping systems (like madMapper or Resolume) and controls its fixtures in a user-friendly space. It has been done after v1. This system also is able to install on machines with AMD architecture. In this version some features like ultra-sonic handler, schedulers, and etc. added to the system. We also implemented multi-link supporting for lightshifter. As in the first version the key point is that we succeed to control to LED boards through raspberry pie and in addition we could control the LED's using ultra-sonic sensors

Technologies: **Softwares and Languages**: Django, DRF, crontab, node-js, express-js, , postgresql, jQuery, sequelize, nginx and etc. **Hardware**: raspberry pie, *ultra-sonic sensor*, *Minix*, and etc.

April 2021 **Programmer**, *GTR* encryption firmware Project, Shinbob Co. Remote Canada.

I checked the encryption system of the GTR corporation and fixed it.

Technologie(s): python

Januery 2021- Full-Stack developer, Lightshifter v1 Project, Shinbob sole. Remote Canada.

March 2021 Lightshifter v1 is a video mapping web-based system, which can connect to mapping systems (like madMapper or Resolume) and controls its fixtures in a user-friendly space. I implemented the lightshifter from scratch. this system is able to install on machines with ARM architecture. It can control the mapping systems using some handlers. The key point is that we succeed to control to LED boards through raspberry pie.

Technologies: **Sotware and languages**: raspberry pie, node-js, express-js, postgresql, jQuery, sequelize, nginx and etc. **Hardware**: **Hardware**: *Raspberry-pie*, *Minix*, and etc.

September Back-end developer, DNBuy project, Shinbob sole Remote Canada.

2020- Dnbuy is an international domain and hosting provider website based in Canada. My task was program-

December ming internal 'API' and synchronizing Dnbuy with Enom using Enom api.

2020 Technologies: Django, Python, Nginx, MySQL, jQuery, and etc.

2015 - 2020 Full-stack django and wordpress developer, Multiple companies, Tehran.

summary Since 2015 to late 2020, I developed UI and APIs for mutiple companies like **Boundar Souban Samaneh**, **Abrbar**, etc. Technologies: django, DRF, postgresql, bootstrap, nginx, wordpress, woocommerce, etc.

## Languages

English Advanced

Turkish Beginner

Arabic **Beginner** 

Japaneses Beginner

## Development and Programming skills

Linux 7 Years User of Linux OS 🛕, wbuntu\*, wbuntu\*,

Backend django framework ★★★★★ flask ★★★☆☆, PHP ★★★☆☆,

Front-end  $\circ$  **Styling**: HTML and CSS  $\bigstar$   $\bigstar$   $\bigstar$   $\bigstar$   $\bigstar$   $\Leftrightarrow$   $\bigstar$  , Bootstrap framework  $\bigstar$   $\bigstar$   $\bigstar$   $\bigstar$ 

• **Programming**: pure javascript  $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Leftrightarrow \mathring{\Box}$ , jQuery  $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Leftrightarrow \mathring{\Box}$ , reactjs  $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Leftrightarrow \mathring{\Box}$ ,

Database ○ MySQL ★★★★★, PostgreSQL ★★★☆

Statistical ○ Programming: R ★ ★ ★ ★ , matlab ★ ★ ☆ ☆

o software: SPSS ★★★☆☆, SAS ★★★☆☆, Tableaue ★★☆☆☆

• Webserver tools: Nginx configuration ★★★☆

o VCS: git ★★★☆, gitflow ★★☆☆

### Interests

Interested in learning New topics in technologies and human languages. Reading stackoverflow and other Stackexchange sites and trying to answer the questions.

## Courses

 AUT and Paris 5 university shared courses on applied statistics (Clustering, Random Forests and Extreme Value Theory)